## **Veysel Usta**

I have been focused on C++ and Typescript. Apart from that, I am researching best practices within the scope of MEVN stack. In the future, my plans include learning technologies that pique my interest such as Redis, Docker, Graph ,Elasticsearch and NextJS. Also I'm a huge docker fan.

Mersin / Turkey (+90) 507 191 64 99 vyslusta1@gmail.com

**PROJECTS** 

**Twitter Clone** — *MongoDB*, *ExpressJS*, *NodeJS*, *Vue.js* 

https://github.com/veyselusta/Twitter

**ConveTube** — *NodeJS*, *ExpressJS* 

https://github.com/veyselusta/ConverTube

https://covertube.herokuapp.com

**Wind** — Vanilla JavaScript - Chrome extension

https://github.com/veyselusta/wind

**Upload** — *MongoDB*, *ExpressJS*, *NodeJS* 

https://github.com/veyselusta/upload

**EXPERIENCE** 

**Digiterra**, Istanbul — Software Developer

MARCH 2021 - PRESENT

Digiterra is a data analytics company that offers software solutions at different levels to companies in their digital transformation journeys to artificial intelligence.

Freelance

OCTOBER 2020 - PRESENT

**EDUCATION** 

**Cukurova University**, Adana — *Degree* 

2017 - 2021

**Automotive Engineering** 

**SKILLS** 

JavaScript

Node.js

Vue.js

React.js

Vuex

MongoDB

Git - Github

C++

**LANGUAGES** 

English